export const quickGame = {
  rows: [
    [
      {
        question: "Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?",
        answer: "Spongebob Squarepants!",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "LMK",
        answer: "Let me know",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What is the first book in the bible?",
        answer: "Genesis",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      { question: "What is the chemical formula for water?", answer: "H2)" },
    ],
    [
      {
        question:
          'What famous cartoon character coined the phrase "Wassup doc?"',
        answer: "Bugs bunny",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "OOTD",
        answer: "Outfit of the day",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "Who parted the red sea?",
        answer: "Moses",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: 'On the periodic table, what does "B" stand for?',
        answer: "Boron",
        doublePoints: true,
      },
    ],
    [
      {
        question: 'What is the snowman\'s name from the movie "Froze"',
        answer: "Olaf",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "IWSTBOOY\n(A threat parents used to make to bad children)",
        answer: "I will slap the black off of you",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "How many days did it take God finish creating earth?",
        answer: "6",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      { question: "What are molecules made of?", answer: "Atoms" },
    ],
    [
      {
        question:
          'What famous anime character goes "Super saiyan" and uses "Kamehameha"',
        answer: "Goku",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      { question: "", answer: "", doublePoints: false, answeredBy: null },
      {
        question: "How many plagues did God send to Egypt?",
        answer: "10",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "Which element has a relative atomic mass of 1?",
        answer: "Hydrogen",
      },
    ],
    [
      {
        question:
          "What is the full name of the famous cartoon character that owns a restaurants that specializes in burgers",
        answer: 'Robert "Bob" Belcher Jr\n(Bob Belcher)',
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      { question: "", answer: "", doublePoints: false, answeredBy: null },
      {
        question: "List the 10 commandments",
        answer:
          "1. You shall have no other gods before Me.\n2. You shall not make idols.\n3. You shall not take the name of the LORD your God in vain.\n4. Remember the Sabbath day, to keep it holy.\n5. Honor your father and your mother.\n6. You shall not murder.\n7. You shall not commit adultery.\n8. You shall not steal.\n9. You shall not bear false witness against your neighbor.\n10. You shall not covet.",
        doublePoints: true,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: " Which chemical element has the symbol 'K'?",
        answer: "Potassium",
      },
    ],
  ],
  rowPoints: [100, 200, 300, 400, 500],
  columnCategories: [
    "Cartoon Time!",
    "IYKYK",
    "John 3:16",
    "Chemically Inclined",
  ],
  columns: 4,
  hoveredCell: { row: null, col: null },
  selectedCell: { rowIndex: 4, colIndex: 3, score: 500 },
};
export const familyGame = {
  rows: [
    [
      {
        question: "What is Brandon's birthday?",
        answer: "October 6th",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the singer whose following is "Bee hive"',
        answer: "Beyonce",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What team did Michael Jordan get drafted to after college?",
        answer: "Chicago Bulls",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What is mommys go to black box frozen dinner?",
        answer: "Lasagna",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "Finish the phrase:\nOne fish, two fish\nRed fish, ________",
        answer: "Blue fish",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
    ],
    [
      {
        question: "What title did mommy receive from Strayer University?",
        answer: "valedictorian",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Finish the lyrics\nTold the doctor I'm a healthy kid\nI smoke ______\nI will run around your\nWhole board like ______",
        answer: "brocolli, monopoly",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question:
          "In boxing, what punch starts from underneath and rises into the target?",
        answer: "Uppercut",
      },
      {
        question: "What nutrient comes from meat, eggs and fish?",
        answer: "protein",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question:
          "When i snap, it'll freeze you in time\nIf youre caught by me, its hard to deny a crime?\n\nWhat am i?",
        answer: "A camera",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
    ],
    [
      {
        question: "What position did Christian play at FIU",
        answer: "Safety (Defensive back)",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: 'What famous rapper is known as "Tunechi"?',
        answer: "Lil Wayne",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the stunt called when the flyer is standing on one leg, and holding the other leg bent with one arm?",
        answer: "Scale",
        doublePoints: true,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What kind of food is tomatoes?",
        answer: "Fruit",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What's the name of the current Jamaican prime minister",
        answer: "Andrew Holness",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
    ],
    [
      {
        question: "What is Uncle Michael middle name?",
        answer: "Dale",
        doublePoints: true,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the name of the Michael Jackson song that features "zombies" in the music video',
        answer: "Thriller",
        doublePoints: true,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "In football, what are all the ways a team can score points?",
        answer: "Touchdown, Safety, Field Goal",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What is the national pie of florida?",
        answer: "Key lime pie",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What is the heaviest organ in the human body?",
        answer: "liver",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
    ],
    [
      {
        question: "What degree(s) does Alyssa have?",
        answer: "IDK tbh, i think she a doctor or sumn",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What year was Rod wave born?",
        answer: "1998",
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the name of the only boxer to have beaten Ryan Garcia",
        answer: 'Gervonte "Tank" Davis',
        doublePoints: false,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What is Aniyah's favorite flavor cake?",
        answer: "Idk tbh, ask her",
        doublePoints: true,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
      {
        question: "What is the name of the greatest character ever?",
        answer: "Mega Man",
        doublePoints: true,
        answeredBy: null,
      },
    ],
  ],
  rowPoints: [100, 200, 300, 400, 500],
  columnCategories: ["Family", "Music", "Sports", "Food", "Random"],
  columns: 5,
  hoveredCell: { row: null, col: null },
  selectedCell: { rowIndex: 1, colIndex: 4, score: 200 },
};
